https://www.critchlow.co.nz/privacy-policy

Last updated: March 2019
Critchlow Geospatial ("us", "we", or "our") operates http://www.critchlow.co.nz/ (our "website"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for improving your experience with using the website and to ensure you receive relevant communications from us. By using our website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information collection and use
While using our website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information that can be used to contact or identify you, or to provide you with content that you have requested from us. This information may include, but is not limited to your first name, last name and email address. If you've asked us to contact you, requested a consultation with us or requested a particular service, we may also ask for your company name, website address and phone number to ensure we can honour this request in the most relevant way possible. From time to time we may also ask you to tell us about your role and responsibilities - this information is used to help us develop and make available content that is relevant to you.
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Marketing Automation Platform tracking code and Google Analytics to collect, monitor and analyse this data.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with marketing emails related to (but not limited to) existing content offers, new content offers, service offerings, event communications, industry news (e.g. blogs and newsletters) and other information. By downloading or registering for any offer on our website, you agree to receive email communications from Critchlow Geospatial. You can unsubscribe from these communications at any time by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link in the footer of our emails.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our website.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of 1st March 2019 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Critchlow Geospatial
Level 6, iCentre, 50 Manners Street, Wellington 6011PO Box 4103, Wellington 6140New Zealand
+64 4 472 8244 (New Zealand)0800 627 746
100% NZ owned and operated
Sign up for our newsletter
Copyright © 2020 Critchlow Geospatial Limited. All Rights Reserved. | Privacy Policy
